A Guide to the Richmond (Va.) Property Records, 1782-1977 (bulk 1920-1977)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Richmond (Va.) Property Records, 1782-1977 (bulk 1920-1977)
Library of Virginia
583.45 cubic feet (1285 boxes); 102 volumes.
Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court; Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court I; Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court II; Richmond (Va.) Chancery Court
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Richmond (Va.) Bills of Sale and Deeds, 1797-1865, involving enslaved and free Black and multiracial individuals are digitized and available through Virginia Untold: The African American Narrative Digital Collection on the Library of Virginia website. Please use digital images.
Acquisition Information
These Records came to the Library of Virginia in shipments of court papers from Richmond City in an undated accession.
Bill of sale, 1837, of Dawson, Marinda, and Polley was purchased by the Library of Viriginia in May 2006 under accession number 42650.
Historical Information
Context for Record Type:
Bills of sale are written agreements which convey title of property, including enslaved people, from seller to buyer. Under the system of chattel slavery, laws permitted enslavers to treat enslaved people as personal possessions in the same manner as livestock, farm equipment, or household items. Enslaved people could be bought or sold without regard to their personal relationships or free will. Bills of sale record the name of the seller, the names of enslaved people being sold and their price, and the name of the buyer. Given that they involved a property transaction, bills of sale were commonly recorded and filed with deeds in the local court. However, there was no official requirement that the transfer of an enslaved person be recorded unless necessary for legal purposes such as a court case or an estate settlement. Enslaved people could also be transferred through a deed of gift, there was no money transaction involved in this case, which distinguishes this record from a bill of sale. Enslavers and their family members often transferred enslaved people between themselves in this manner.
Deeds are written agreements which convey title of property, such as an enslaved person, from one individual to another. These include the voluntary transfer of enslaved people between family members with no financial transaction involved. Deeds include the names of the grantors, grantees, and enslaved people. Clerks proved, acknowledged, and recorded deeds in the local court.
Types of Courts:
Richmond (Va.) Hustings court created by the General Assembly in 1782 at the time Richmond was granted it's charter. The court was created to handle all criminal cases, civil law cases, probate of wills, fiduciary accounts, deed recordings, all licenses (business, marriage, etc.), citizenship applications, etc. It also included the Mayor's Court.
Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court Part I was approved April 5, 1910 under agreement of consolidation between the City of Richmond and the City of Manchester and their corporation/ Hustings Court. It was created to handle all criminal cases, civil law cases, probate of wills, fiduciary accounts, deed recordings, all licenses (business, marriage, etc.), citizenship applications, etc.
Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court Part II was created in 1874 as the Corporation or Hustings Court of the City of Manchester, by act of 1906 the General Assembly provided that under terms of Richmond and Manchester Approved April 1910 that the corporation court should be retained and continued as the court of consolidated municipality and was designation Husting Court of the City of Richmond Part II. It was created to handle all criminal cases, civil law cases, probate of wills, fiduciary accounts, deed recordings, all licenses (business, marriage, etc.), etc. south of the James River.
Richmond (Va.) Chancery Court created by the General Assembly in 1870 with the first session held in June 1870. It was created to handle all probate of wills, fiduciary accounts, deed recordings and other chancery related matters. All records of deeds previously records in Hustings court transferred to this court. All wills probated and fiduciary accounts transferred from Hustings Court to this court. All wills, etc. probated in Circuit Court transferred to this court.
Husting Court part I, Husting Court Part II, Circuit Court, Chancery Court, and Law and Equity Court merged July 1, 1973 to become Circuit Court of the City of Richmond Division II ( now Circuit Court of the City of Richmond, Manchester Court House)
Locality History Note: The city of Richmond, located between Henrico and Chesterfield Counties, was named by William Byrd (1674-1744), who envisioned the development of a city at the falls of the James River and with the help of William Mayo laid out the town in 1737. The name probably came from the English borough of Richmond upon Thames, which Byrd visited on several occasions. Richmond was established in 1742 and in 1779 was designated the capital of Virginia effective 30 April 1780. It was incorporated as a town, although "stiled the city of Richmond," in 1782 and was incorporated as a city in 1842. It served as the capital of the Confederacy from mid-1861 to April 1865. Richmond was enlarged by the annexation of Manchester (or South Richmond) in 1910, and by the addition of Barton Heights, Fairmount, and Highland Park in 1914. Further annexations from Chesterfield County occurred in 1942 and 1970.
Lost Records Note: During the burning of Richmond on April 3, 1865, during the Civil War, Richmond circuit court judge John A. Meredith led efforts to save the circuit court records found at the State Court House. Rescuers successfully removed all the papers that were necessary to pending suits and many of the order books, but all of the wills and deed books were lost. Records of the superior court and circuit superior court of law and chancery were also destroyed. Most of the pre-Civil War Hustings Court records exist.
Scope and Content
Richmond (Va.) Property Records, 1782-1977, remain largely unprocessed but consist primarily of deeds which include deeds of bargain and sale, deeds of gift, mortgages, bills of sale, and deeds of trust. Included are three boxes of processed material consisting of bills of sale and deeds,1784-1964, involving free and enslaved Black individuals.
Deeds of bargain and sale are the most recorded deed in which one individual sells property, usually land, but occasionally personal property, to another individual. Such deeds show the names of the grantor and grantee, the residence of both parties, a description of what is being sold, the consideration (or price), the location of the tract of land, the tract's boundaries, and any limitations on the property being sold. The deed was signed by the grantor, and possibly his wife or anyone else having a claim to the property, and by at least two witnesses. Appended to the deed may be a memorandum of livery of seisin, stating that the property has changed hands and that peaceful possession has taken place.
Deeds of gift are often found transferring property, either real or personal including enslaved people, from one individual to another "for love and affection." The degree of kinship, if any, between the grantor and grantee is sometimes stated. Information recorded included name(s) of the grantor(s), grantee(s), and enslaved people. Deeds of gift were proved and recorded in the local court.
Mortgages and deeds of trust were deeds where one party is indebted to another and transfers or mortgages property to a third party to secure the debt.
Bills of sale are written agreements which convey title of property, such as an enslaved person, from seller to buyer. Bills of sale record the name of the seller, the names of enslaved persons being sold and their price, and the name of the buyer. Given that they involved a property transaction, bills of sale were commonly recorded and filed with deeds in the local court.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into two series
Series I: Deeds and bills of sale,1784-1864, involving free and enslaved people, arranged chronologically
Series II: Deeds and records related to, 1782-1977, largely unprocessed but loosely arranged chronologically; Subseries A: Deeds, 1789-1977; Subseries B: Index to Deeds, 1782-1923; Subseries C: Release Deeds, 1820-1957
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
See also: Richmond (Va.) Deeds of Emancipation, 1792-1865
Records related to free and enslaved people of Richmond (Va.) and other localities are available through the Virginia Untold: The African American Narrative Digital Collection on the Library of Virginia website.
Additional Richmond (Va.) court records can be found on microfilm at the Library of Virginia.Consult "A Guide to Virginia County and City Records on Microfilm."
Richmond City is one of Virginia's Lost Records Localities. Additional Richmond City Court Records may be found in the Lost Records Localities Digital Collection on the Library of Virginia website.
Contents List
- Deeds and Bills of Sale: relating to free and enslaved Black and multiracial persons, 1784-1864, 1.8 cubic feet(4 boxes)
  digitized and available through Virginia Untold: The African American Narrative Digital Collection on the Library of Virginia website. Please use digital images.
  Chronological
  - Deeds, Agreements, etc. (Free and Enslaved People) 1784-1832
  - Deeds, Agreements, etc. (Free and Enslaved People) 1790
  - Deeds, Agreements, etc. (Free and Enslaved People) 1833-1847
  - Deeds, Agreements, etc. (Free and Enslaved People) 1848-1864
  - Bill of sale 1837 Not digitized at this time
- Deeds and records related to, 1782-1977, 581.45 cubic feet(1051 boxes); 102 volumes
  These records are largely unprocessed. They include loose deeds; bound index to deeds as well as loose and bound release deeds.
  Series are alphabetical by record type; records are loosely chronological within series
  - Deeds, 1789-1977, 477.85 cubic feet(1055 boxes); 1 volume
    These records are largely unprocessed. Included are deeds recorded in the Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court, Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court Divison I, Richmond (Va.) Hustings Court Division II; and Richmond (Va.) Chancery Court. The majorty of post 1910 deeds appear to be Husting Court Divison II.
    Loosely Chronological
    - Unrecorded Deeds, Deeds, Apprenticeship Indentures, Officials' Bonds ( A-H ) 1789-1864
    - Deeds, Apprenticeship Indentures, Officials' Bonds ( H-L ) 1790-1818
    - Deeds, Apprenticeship Indentures, Officials' Bonds ( M-Z ) 1790-1818 circa
    - Deeds ( R-V ) 1794-1818
    - Deeds ( W-Z ) 1800-1819
    - Deeds ( C, D, E, F ) 1801-1817
    - Deeds ( A-B; B ) 1813; 1792-1818
    - Deeds 1820 Febuary-1821 August
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 16-19 ) 1820 Febuary-1821 August
    - Deeds,Plat 1820 January -1825 May, 1827 May
    - Deeds 1821 Septmeber-1823 October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 19-23 ) 1822 January-1825 May
    - Deeds 1823 November-1825 November
    - Deeds 1825 December-1828 July
    - Deeds, Unrecorded Deeds ( Deed Books 25-56 ) 1825 July-1849 August; 1832
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 25-37 ) 1826 October-1837 June
    - Deeds 1828 August-1831 Febuary
    - Deeds Wrappers 1828-1830
    - Deeds 1831 March-1833 December
    - Deeds 1834 January-1836 May
    - Deeds 1836 June-1838 March
    - Limited partnerships, mechanics leins, deeds of trust, chancery decrees, plats, receipts, articles of incorporation, wills, bonds/commissions/oaths, memorandum dockets 1837-1909 circa
    - Deeds 1838 Aprilil-1840 March
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 40-59 ) 1839 August-1849 October
    - Deeds 1840 April-1842 Febuary
    - Deeds 1842 Febuary-1843 August
    - Deeds 1843 Septmeber-1845 May
    - Deeds 1845 May-1846 April
    - Deeds 1846 April-1847 April
    - Deeds 1846-1847
    - Deeds 1847 May-1848 May
    - Deeds 1848 May-1849 July
    - Deeds 1849 August-1850 July
    - Deeds 1850 August-1851 July
    - Deeds 1851 August-1852 June
    - Deeds 1852 July-1853 July
    - Deeds 1853 July-1854 March
    - Deeds 1854 March-December
    - Copies of Court Orders and Deeds 1854-1861
    - Deeds 1855 January-1856 January
    - Deeds 1856 Januaryuary-Decemberember
    - Deeds 1857 January-October
    - Deeds 1857 November-1858 March
    - Deeds 1858 April-1859 Febuary
    - Deeds 1859 March-1860 March
    - Deeds 1860 January-1861 April
    - Deeds 1861 May-December
    - Deeds 1862 January-1863 December
    - Deeds 1864 January-1865 December
    - Deeds and Contracts, etc. 1865
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 82A-83B ) 1866 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 83A-84B, List of Deeds ) 1867 January-April
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 84B-87A ) 1867 May-1868 December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 85B-89A ) 1868 June-1869 June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 89A-90A, Deed Books 88B-90B ) 1869 July-1870 March
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 91A-92B ) 1870 Febuary-Septmeber
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 92B, 96A, 96B, List of Deeds ) 1870 October-1871 January
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 93B-95B, Deed Books 96A-97A, List of Deeds, 96A-99C ) 1871 Febuary-March
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 97A-99A, Deed Books 96B-97B ) 1872 April-1873 Febuary
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 98C-99C; Deed Books 100-101A, Deed Books 100B-101B ) 1872 July-1873; 1873 March-Septmeber
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 100C-101C; Deed Books 101A-102A; Deed Books 102A-104A; List of Deeds, Deed Books 101A-104C ) 1873 March-Septmeber; 1873 October-December; 1874 January-December; 1873 October-1874 December
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 101B, Deed Books 101C-102C; Deed Books 102B-104B; Deed Books 102C-103C ) 1873 October-December; 1874 January-December; 1874 January-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 104C-106C ) 1874 January-1876 January
    - Deeds 1874-1883
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 106C-107C; List of Deeds, Index; Deed Books 107A-109A; Deed Book 107B ) 1875 August-December; 1876 January-December; 1876 Febuary-December; 1876 Febuary
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 108B-109B; Deed Books 107C-108C; Deed Book 109C ) 1876 April-December; 1876 March-July; 1876 Septmeber-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 109B-111B, List of Deeds Index, Deed Books 109A-111A ) 1877 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 111B; Deed Books 112A-113A ) 1877 November-December; 1877 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 113A; Deed Books 111B-113B, Deed Books 111C-113C ) 1878 November-December; 1878 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 113A; Deed Books 111C-113C ) 1878 November-December; 1878 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 114B-115B; Deed Books 113C-115C ) 1879 Febuary-December; 1879 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 114A-115A, List of Deed Indexes ) 1879 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 115C-117C ) 1880 January-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds Index; Deed Books 115A-117A; Deed Books 116B-117B ) 1880 January-December; 1880 January-Febuary, April-December; 1880 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 117A-119A, List of Deeds Index ) 1881 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 117B-119B; Deed Books 118C-119C ) 1881 January-November; 1881 January-December
    - Deeds and plats re: Condemnations 1881-1905
    - Deeds, Plats-Blueprints 1881-1946
    - Deeds ( List of Deed Index, Deed Books 119A-122A, Deed Books 120B-122B ) 1882 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 120B-122B; Deed Books 120C-122C ) 1882 June-December; 1882 January-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds Index, Deed Books 123A-124A; Deed Books 122B-124B ) 1883 January-December; 1883 January-June, Septmeber-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 122C-124C; List of Deeds Index; Deed Books 125A-126A ) 1883 January-December; 1884 January-August; 1884 January-July
    - Deeds 1883-1886
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 125C-127C; List of Deeds Index; Deed Books 127A-128A ) 1884 April-December; 1885 January-December; 1885 January -May
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds Index; Deed Books 126A-127A; Deed Books 125B-127B; Deed Book 125C ) 1884 October-December; 1884 August-December; 1884 January-December; 1884 January-March
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 128A-129A; Deed Books 127B-129B; Deed Books 127C-128C ) 1885 July-November; 1885 January-December; 1885 Febuary-May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 128C-129C; List of Deeds Index, Deed Books 129A-131A ) 1885 May-December; 1886 January-December
    - Unrecorded Deeds and Charters 1885-1913
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 129B-131B, Deed Books 129C-131C ) 1886 January-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes, Deed Books 131A-134A; Deed Books 131B-133B ) 1887 January-December; 1887 January-July
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 133B-134B; Deed Books 131C-134C; Deed Book 134A ) 1887 July-December; 1887 January-December; 1888 January-June
    - Deeds 1887-1888
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 135A-136A; Deed Books 134B-136B; Deed Books 134C-136C ) 1888 July-December; 1888 January-December; 1888 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 136C; Deed Books 136A-139A ) 1888 November-December; 1889 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 138C-139C; Lists of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Index; Deed Books 139A-141A ) 1889 August-December; 1890 January-December; 1890 January-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 139A; Deed Books 136B-138B ) 1889 November-December; 1889 January-Septmeber
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 138B; Deed Books 136C-138C ) 1889 Septmeber-December; 1889 January-April
    - Deeds 1889-1891
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 141A-142A; Deed Books 139B-140B ) 1890 June-December; 1890 January-May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 140B-142B; Deed Books 139C-142C ) 1890 May-December; 1890 January-December
    - Railroad Deeds 1890-1915 [1878-1924]
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 142B-144B ) 1891 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 142C-144C ) 1891 January-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Index; Deed Books 142A-144A ) 1891 January-December; 1891 January
    - Deeds 1891-1893
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 147A; Deed Books 144B-147B ) 1892 November-December; 1892 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 147B; Deed Books 144C-146C ) 1892 October-December; 1892 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 147C; List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 147A-149A ) 1892 October-December; 1893 January-December; 1893 January-July
    - Deeds ( List of Deed Indexes; Deed Books 144A-147A ) 1892; 1892 January-November
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 149B-150B; Deed Books 147C-149C ) 1893 August-December; 1893 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 149C-150C; List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Book 151A ) 1893 August-December; 1894; 1894 January-May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 149A-150A; Deed Books 147B-149B ) 1893 June-December; 1893 January-July
    - Deeds, etc. 1893-1896
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 152B-153B; Deed Books 150C-151C ) 1894 July-December; 1894 January-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 152C-153C; List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Book 153A ) 1894 June-December; 1895 January-December; 1895 January-Febuary
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 151A-153A; Deed Books 150B-152B ) 1894 May-December; 1894 January-July
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 155C-156C; List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 156A-157A ) 1895 August-December; 1896; 1896 January-March
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 154A-155A ) 1895 March-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 155A-156A; Deed Books 153B-155B ) 1895 November-December; 1895 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 155B-156B; Deed Books 153C-155C ) 1895 October-December; 1895 January-July
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 159C; List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 159A-161A ) 1896 December; 1897 January-December; 1897 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 156B-159B ) 1896 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 156C-159C ) 1896 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 157A-159A; Deed Book 156B ) 1896 March-December; 1896 January
    - Deeds, etc. 1896-1900
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 160C-162C ) 1897 April-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 160B-162B; Deed Books 159C-160C ) 1897 June-December; 1897 January-April
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 161A-162A; Deed Books 159B-160B ) 1897October-December; 1897 January-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 161B-164B ) 1898 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 162C-164C ) 1898 January-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Book 162A; Deed Book 163A; Deed Book 164A ) 1898 January-December; 1898 January-May; 1898 May-October; 1898 October-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 164A-166A ) 1899 January-December; 1899 January-Septmeber
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 166B-167B; Deed Books 164C-166C ) 1899 October-December; 1899 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 166C-167C; Deed Books 167C-169C ) 1899 October-December; 1900 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 166A-167A; Deed Books 164B-166B ) 1899 Septmeber-December; 1899 January-October
    - Deeds and Records 1899-1910 circa
    - Deeds ( Lists of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 167A-169A ) 1900 January-December; 1900 January-Septmeber
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 169A-172 B; List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes ) 1900 January-Septmeber; 1901 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 169A; Deed Books 167B-169B ) 1900 October-December; 1900 January-December
    - Deeds, etc. 1900-1903
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 170C-172C ) 1901 April-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 171B-172B; Deed Books 169C-170C ) 1901 August-December; 1901 January-April
    - Deeds ( Deed Book 172A; Deed Books 169A-171B ) 1901 Septmeber, 1901 July-December; 1901 January-August
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 172C-176C ) 1902 January-December
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 172A-174A ) 1902 January-December; 1902 January-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 174A-175A; Deed Books 172B-173B ) 1902 June-December; 1902 January-May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 174B-176B ) 1902 May-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 176B-177B; Deed Book 176C ) 1903 April-December; 1903 January-March
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 176A-177A ) 1903 January-December; 1903 January-May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 177A-179A; Deed Books 176B-177B ) 1903 June-December; 1903 January-March
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 177C-179C ) 1903 March-December
    - Deeds, etc. 1903-1908
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 179A-181A ) 1904 January-December; 1904 January-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 181C-183C ) 1904 July-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 181A-183A; Deed Books 197B-180B ) 1904 July-December; 1904 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 187B-192B ) 1904 March-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 182B-183B; Deed Book 193D ) 1904 November-December; 1904 January-July
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 184B-187B ) 1905 April-1906 January
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 184-187A; Deed Books 183B-184B ) 1905 April-December; 1905 January-April
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes; Deed Books 183A-184A ) 1905 January-December; 1905 January-April
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 183C-186C ) 1905 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 186C-187C; List of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Indexes ) 1905 October-January 1906; 1906 Febuary-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 187A-190A ) 1906 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 190B-191B ) 1906 July-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 188C-191C ) 1906 May-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 190A-191A; Deed Books 187B-189B ) 1906 October-December; 1906 Febuary-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 193A-196A ) 1907 April-1908 January
    - Deeds ( List of Deeds Index Grantor/Grantee Indexes, Deed Books 191A-193A ) 1907 January-December
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 191B-194B ) 1907 January-October
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 194D-196D ) 1907 July-1908 May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 193C-196C; Deed Book 193D ) 1907 May-1908 January; 1907 April-June
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 195B-196B; Deed Books 191C-193C ) 1907 October-1908 January; 1907 January-May
    - Deeds ( Deed Books 196C-199C ) 1908 Febuary-December
    - Deeds ( Lists of Deeds, Grantor/Grantee Index; Deed Book 195A-197A ) 1908 January-December; 1908 Febuary-May